{"title": "Rescueland Planets!", "difficulty": 5, "randomOrder": false, "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "What is the capital of Rescueland?", "correctAnswer": "Non-existent", "wrongAnswers": ["Erros", "The Great Computer", "Lumen City"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who leads Titan?", "correctAnswer": "Monoquia", "wrongAnswers": ["Zoltar", "Erros", "The Great Computer"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the atmosphere composition of Hermonochy?", "correctAnswer": "Hydrogen 86%, Helium 11%, Methane 2%", "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 60%, Nitrogen 30%, Argon 10%", "Nitrogen 70%, Oxygen 20%, Sulfur Dioxide 10%", "Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "How many interceptors does Ralfialand have?", "correctAnswer": "2200", "wrongAnswers": ["30", "5000", "2400"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the tech level of Klesone?", "correctAnswer": "10", "wrongAnswers": ["9", "11", "12"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which planet is the most powerful superpower?", "correctAnswer": "Helucky", "wrongAnswers": ["Recola", "Rescueland", "Titan"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the capital of Bad Guy Land?", "correctAnswer": "Del", "wrongAnswers": ["Ilines", "Dakhem", "Gorath"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the atmosphere of Aquarion primarily composed of?", "correctAnswer": "Water Vapour 70%, Oxygen 20%, Nitrogen 10%", "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%", "Oxygen 40%, Argon 30%, Carbon Dioxide 30%", "Nitrogen 70%, Hydrogen 20%, Oxygen 10%"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who is the leader of Recola?", "correctAnswer": "Emperor Astan", "wrongAnswers": ["Zoltar", "Monoquia", "Erros"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the population of Titan?", "correctAnswer": "7,200 trillion", "wrongAnswers": ["7.9 billion", "34.2 quadrillion", "800 trillion"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the tech level of N2?", "correctAnswer": "1", "wrongAnswers": ["5", "6", "3"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the primary gas in the atmosphere of Glaciera?", "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 60%", "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen 30%", "Methane 25%", "Carbon Dioxide 20%"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who leads the Imperium?", "correctAnswer": "Xarendos", "wrongAnswers": ["King Coators", "Governor Ecard", "Luncil"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the main focus of Keluha's economy?", "correctAnswer": "Crystalline resources", "wrongAnswers": ["Agriculture", "Technology", "Mining"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the population of Yelthia?", "correctAnswer": "90 billion", "wrongAnswers": ["150 million", "50 million", "2 trillion"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which planet has the largest army size?", "correctAnswer": "Rescueland", "wrongAnswers": ["Helucky", "Recola", "Titan"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the power status of Aquarion?", "correctAnswer": "3800000000/6000000000", "wrongAnswers": ["2900000000/6000000000", "6000000000/6000000000", "5000000000/6000000000"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who rules Recola?", "correctAnswer": "Emperor Astan", "wrongAnswers": ["Commander of War Weda", "The Great Computer", "Luncil"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the total ground force of Helucky?", "correctAnswer": "37 septillion", "wrongAnswers": ["37 trillion", "37 billion", "37 quadrillion"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the capital of Wana?", "correctAnswer": "Nezon", "wrongAnswers": ["Havenford", "Ironhold", "Fres City"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the tech level of Ukakia?", "correctAnswer": "8", "wrongAnswers": ["7", "6", "9"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which planet is characterized by expansive forests and oceans?", "correctAnswer": "Wehaya", "wrongAnswers": ["N2", "Aquarion", "Helucky"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the atmosphere of Loaa primarily composed of?", "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 60%, Nitrogen 20%, Water vapor 15%", "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%", "Oxygen 70%, Nitrogen 20%, Argon 10%", "Oxygen 50%, Nitrogen 40%, Methane 10%"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the main focus of the economy in Nara?", "correctAnswer": "Energy harvesting from storms", "wrongAnswers": ["Mining", "Agriculture", "Technology"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the primary gas in the atmosphere of Aquarion?", "correctAnswer": "Water Vapour", "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Helium"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the capital of the Mega Bad Guy Land?", "correctAnswer": "Ilines", "wrongAnswers": ["Dakhem", "Gorath", "Del"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the leader of Heloa?", "correctAnswer": "Luncil", "wrongAnswers": ["King Coators", "The Great Computer", "High Lord Tacer"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the tech level of Fufe?", "correctAnswer": "5", "wrongAnswers": ["6", "7", "8"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the power status of Imperium?", "correctAnswer": "6125487350/6000000000", "wrongAnswers": ["6000000000/6000000000", "4900000000/6000000000", "3200000000/6000000000"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who is the leader of Wonto?", "correctAnswer": "Tsar Protader", "wrongAnswers": ["Luncil", "King Coators", "The Great Computer"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the capital of Naha?", "correctAnswer": "Starlight Haven", "wrongAnswers": ["Fres City", "Havenford", "Filaga"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the atmosphere of Titan composed of?", "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 57%, Nitrogen 33%, Argon 6%, CO2 3%", "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen 70%, Oxygen 20%, Argon 10%", "Oxygen 60%, Helium 30%, Trace gases 10%", "Oxygen 50%, Nitrogen 40%, Carbon Dioxide 10%"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the leader of Ehana?", "correctAnswer": "High Lord Tacer", "wrongAnswers": ["Kahn Coars", "Xarendos", "Erros"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the total ground force of Recola?", "correctAnswer": "146 hexillion", "wrongAnswers": ["90 million", "1 trillion", "7 billion"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the population of Filto?", "correctAnswer": "45 trillion", "wrongAnswers": ["50 trillion", "60 trillion", "40 trillion"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the capital of Klesone?", "correctAnswer": "Rrinai", "wrongAnswers": ["Filoho", "Lumen City", "Nezon"], "timeout": 10}]}